Tanya M Coleman

Technical Project Manager

Sun City Center, FL

727-851-1913 | tanya.coleman99@outlook.com LinkedIn I

SUMMARY

I am a Technical Project Manager who is proficient in communication and reporting, risk management, problem-solving, and project management methodologies. I have a two year background in office and team management which helped me develop my skills as an active listener, organizer, and motivator. I have a strong interest in web development, which has led me to take courses in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.

SKILLS

Project Management Skills: Learned in Project Life Cycle, Systems Development Life Cycle, Scrum workflow, Agile, Waterfall and Predictive methodologies, Negotiation, Risk Management, Research

Processes: Well versed in Stakeholder management, Risk Assessment and management, Estimating and Budgeting, Budget management, Project documentation, and Team Collaboration

Tools: Slack, Jira, Wrike, Asana, Trello, Monday.com, Excel, Microsoft Office, Outlook, Zoom

PROJECTS

XYZ Website Build | Thinkful Capstone Project

 Successfully planned and documented a website build project creating pertinent documents such as stakeholder requirements log, business requirements documents, milestone schedules, functional and non-functional requirements documents, project charter, SDLC document, Agile product backlog document, budget summary, project approval requirements document, and requirements register. Conducted a project kickoff meeting via Zoom. Created and communicated a team charter. Completed a stakeholder engagement matrix and project communication plan.

Training Module | Humana At Home

Successfully created a comprehensive training module for a Referral Specialists role used to train new associates.
 Wrote detailed training material for both end-users and trainers. Planned and presented training material, led stakeholders' meetings, trained leaders on materials. Communicated clearly throughout the development of the training module to stakeholders, leaders, and end-users.

EXPERIENCE

Care Management Support Specialist II

Humana | Remote

August 2019 – November 2021

- Introduced members and industry professionals to resources available within their policy to cover medical needs.
- Initiated engagement of members and care managers in an effort to align members with personalized medical
- Actively worked with nurses to engage members in available resources.
- Collaborated with industry professionals to direct members to available resources.

Triage Specialist

Humana | Remote

January 2013- August 2019

- Aligned member's medical records with member profiles
- Effectively collaborated with industry leaders and medical professionals to determine best course of action for members
- Measured member qualifications for various resources

Referral Specialist

Humana | St. Petersburg, FL

March 2011- January 2013

- Conducted member interviews for care management services
- Took initiative to develop and implement a training module for the referral specialist role

EDUCATION

Technical Project Management

April 2022

Thinkful

• Completed an extensive online course in Technical Project Management where I learned and practiced principles governed by PMI and the Agile mindset as is dictated by the Scrum workflow. Learned and practiced project management principles like the System Development Life Cycle, Project Life Cycle, and Predictive methodologies.

Certified Scrum Master April 2022
Six Sigma Global Institute

•